poachedjobs.com 2017-07-10

# Privacy | Restaurant Jobs – Poached Jobs

## Poached Privacy Policy

We take your privacy seriously, and this Privacy Policy is meant to help you understand what information we collect and why we collect it. We encourage you to take the time to read this policy and contact us with any concerns you may have. This policy contains information about:

. What personally identifiable information is collected from you through the website, how it is used and with whom it may be shared.  
. Our Registration requirements and related policies.  
. What cookies we use, and why.  
. Our policy regarding links to other sites.  
. Our use of the Google Maps API.  
. What choices are available to you regarding the use of your data.  
. The security procedures in place to protect the misuse of your information.

### Information Collection, Use, and Sharing

We are the sole owners of the information collected on poachedjobs.com. We only have access to/collect information that you voluntarily give us via email, registration or other direct contact. We do not sell or rent this personal information to anyone.  
We will use your information to respond to you, regarding the reason you contacted us. We will not share your personal information with any third party outside of our organization, other than as necessary to fulfill your request, e.g. to assist you with a purchase of a job listing or some other service. We do share aggregated demographic information with our partners and advertisers. This is not linked to any personal information that can identify any individual person.  
Unless you ask us not to, we may contact you via email in the future to tell you about specials, new products or services, or changes to this privacy policy.  
Registration In order to use this website, a user must first complete the registration form. During registration a user is required to give certain information (such as name and email address). This information is used to contact you about the products/services on our site in which you have expressed interest. You may also be asked for demographic information about yourself, but it is not required.

### Cookies

We use “cookies” on this site. A cookie is a piece of data stored on a site visitor’s hard drive to help us improve your access to our site and identify repeat visitors to our site. For instance, when we use a cookie to identify you, you would not have to log in a password more than once, saving you time while on our site. Cookies can also enable us to track and target the interests of our users to enhance the experience on our site. Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information on our site. Some of our business partners may use cookies on our site (for example, advertisers). However, we have no access to or control over these cookies.

### Links To Other Sites

Poached contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the content or privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of any other site that collects personally identifiable information.

### Google Maps API

Poached utilizes the Google Maps API for job postings and other services. You can learn more about Google’s [privacy policies here](https://www.google.com/policies/privacy/ "Google Privacy Policy").

### Your Access to and Control Over Information

You may opt out of any future contacts from us at any time. You can do the following at any time by contacting us via the email address given on our website:  
• See what data we have about you, if any.  
• Change/correct any data we have about you.  
• Have us delete any data we have about you.  
• Express any concern you have about our use of your data.

### Security

We take precautions to protect your information. When you submit sensitive information via the website, your information is protected both online and offline.  
Wherever we collect sensitive information (such as credit card data), that information is encrypted and transmitted to us in a secure way. You can verify this by looking for a closed lock icon at the bottom of your web browser, or looking for “https” at the beginning of the address of the web page.  
While we use encryption to protect sensitive information transmitted online, we also protect your information offline. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, billing or customer service) are granted access to personally identifiable information. The computers/servers in which we store personally identifiable information are kept in a secure environment.

### Updates

Our Privacy Policy may change from time to time and all updates will be posted on this page.  
If you feel that we are not abiding by this privacy policy, you should contact us immediately via email: [hello@poachedjobs.com](mailto:hello@poachedjobs.com?subject=privacy%20policy%20questions)
